A Guide to the Thomas Inge papers, 1879-2001
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series I - Comic Arts
  - Sub-series C - Published and Unpublished Works by Others
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1974, 1975 (Box 18)
      September 3 - December 31
      1975: January 1 - 13
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1975 (Box 19)
      1975: January 14 - July 11
      July 14 - 30
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1975 (Box 20)
      1975: July 31 - October 4
      October 6 - December 20
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1974, 1975, 1976 (Box 21)
      1974: September 4
      1975: December 22 - 31
      1976: January 1 - 31
    - La Noche, #8, October 1981, Brazil (Box 21)
    - La Noche, #9, November 1981, Brazil (Box 21)
    - La Opinión, #135, October 10, 1971, Argentina (Box 21)
    - La Opinión, #140, October 17, 1971, Argentina (Box 21)
    - The Black Panther Intercommunal News Service, Vol. VII #21, January 15, 1972 (Box 21)
    - El Diario Austral, December 3, 1971, Chile (Box 21)
    - El Diario Austral, December 4, 1971, Chile (Box 21)
    - El Diario Austral, December 7, 1971, Chile (Box 21)
    - The Second Section: Boston After Dark, March 28, 1972 (Box 21)
    - The Phoenix: Boston's Weekly Newspaper, March 29, 1972 (Box 21)
    - The New York Review of Books, Vol. XIX #6, October 19, 1972 (Box 21)
    - The Student Mobilizer, October 6, early 1970s (Box 21)
    - Eat: The Paper for the Orally Minded, Vol. 1 #15, no date (Box 21)
    - The Oxford Eagle, Vol. 108 #191, August 6, 1976, Oxford, Mississippi (Box 21)
    - The Oxford Eagle, Vol. 114 #191, July 3, 1982, Oxford, Mississippi (Box 21)
    - The Oxford Eagle, Vol. 114 #192, August 2, 1982, Oxford, Mississippi (Box 21)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1973 (Box 22)
      1973: June 17, 24
      July 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
      Aug 5, 12, 19, 26
      Sept 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      Oct 7, 14, 21, 28
      Nov 4, 11, 25
      Dec 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1974 (Box 23)
      1974: Jan 6, 13, 20, 27
      Feb 3, 10, 17, 24
      Mar 3, 10, 17, 24, 31
      Apr 7, 14, 21, 28
      May 12, 19, 26
      June 9, 16, 23, 30
      July 7, 14, 21, 28
      Aug 4, 11, 18, 25
      Sept 1, 8, 15, 29
      Oct 6, 13, 20, 27
      Nov 3, 10, 17, 24
      Dec 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1975 (Box 24)
      1975: Jan 5, 19, 26
      Feb 2, 9, 16, 23
      Mar 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      Apr 6, 13, 20, 27
      May 4, 11, 18, 25
      June 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
      July 6, 13, 20, 27
      Aug 3, 10, 17, 24, 31
      Sept 7, 14, 21, 28
      Oct 5, 12, 19, 26
      Nov 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      Dec 7, 14, 21, 28
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1976 (Box 25)
      1976: Jan 4, 11, 18, 25
      Feb 8, 15, 22, 29
      Mar 7, 14, 21, 28
      Apr 4, 11, 18, 25
      May 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      June 13, 20, 27
      July 4, 11, 18, 25
      Aug 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
      Sept 5, 12, 19, 26
      Oct 3, 10, 17, 24, 31
      Nov 7, 14, 21, 28
      Dec 5, 12, 19, 26
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1977 (Box 26)
      1977: Jan 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      Feb 6, 13, 20, 27
      Mar 6, 13, 20, 27
      Apr 3, 10, 17, 24
      May 1, 8, 15,
      Aug 14, 21,
      Sep 4, 11, 18, 25
      Oct 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      Nov 6, 13, 20, 27
      Dec 4, 11, 18, 25
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1978 (Box 27)
      1978: Jan 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
      Feb 5, 12, 19, 26
      Mar 5, 12, 19, 26
      Apr 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
      May 7, 14, 21, 28
      June 4, 11, 18
      July 21, 30
      Aug 6, 13, 20
      Sept 3, 10, 17, 24
      Oct 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
      Nov 5, 12, 19, 26
      Dec 3, 10, 17, 24, 31
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1979 (Box 28)
      1979: Jan 7, 14, 21, 28
      Feb 4, 11, 18, 25
      Mar 4, 11, 18, 25
      Apr 1, 8, 22, 29
      May 6, 13, 20, 27
      June 2, 10, 17, 24
      Nov 4, 11, 18, 25
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1980 (Box 29)
      1980: Jan 13, 20, 27
      June 1, 8, 15, 22
    - The Atlanta Journal and Constitution, Sunday Comics: Nov 18, 1973 (Box 29)
    - The Charlotte News, Sunday Comics: Jan 1, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Sunday News, (New York) Sunday Comics: Mar 24, 1974; Dec 29, 1974 (Box 29)
    - The Washington Post, Sunday Comics: Sept 19, 1976; Oct 31, 1976; Jan 1, 1979 (Box 29)
    - The Weekend Citizen (Ottawa, Canada) Sunday Comics: June 23, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black and White Daily Comics: Feb 2 - Aug 7, 1976 (Box 29)
    - The New York Column: Vol. 3 #439 December 4 - 10, 1970 (Box 29)
    - The Mail on Sunday Cartoons (London, England): #105 May 5, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous Color Sunday Comics Clippings (Box 29)
    - America's Greatest Comic Weekly, Sundays 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938 (Box 30)
      1934: Aug 19, 26
      Sept 9, 16, 30
      Dec 2, 9, 16, 23
      1935: July 21
      Aug 11
      Sep 8, 15, 22
      Oct 6, 20, 27
      Nov 3, 24
      Dec 1, 8, 15, 29
      1936: Mar 29
      May 3
      Dec 6, 13, 20, 27
      1937: Feb 7
      Apr 18
      May 2
      Sept 19
      Oct 17
      1938: Jan 2, 9, 16, 23, 30
    - Cinema 5 Entertainment Catalogue, 1978 (Box 31)
    - Interview, IX #1, January 1979 (Box 31)
    - Interview, IX #2, February 1979 (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles Times West Magazine, April 28, 1968 (Box 31)
    - The Nashville Tennessean, Sunday May 29, 1960 (Box 31)
    - New York Times, Arts & Leisure Section, Sunday July 4, 1976 (Box 31)
    - New York Times Magazine, Sunday July 4, 1976 (Box 31)
      Special Issue: "America at 200"
    - New York Times Book Review, Sunday July 4, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Rolling Stone, #132 April 12, 1973 (Box 31)
    - The Village Voice, Vol. XXIV #32, August 6, 1979 (Box 31)
    - John F. Kennedy Assassination
      - Richmond News Leader, Friday November 22, 1963 (Box 32)
      - Richmond Times Dispatch, Saturday November 23, 1963 (Box 32)
      - Richmond News Leader, Saturday November 23, 1963 (Box 32)
      - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday November 24, 1963 (Box 32)
      - Richmond Times Dispatch, Monday November 25, 1963 (Box 32)
      - Richmond News Leader, Monday November 25, 1963 (Box 32)
      - Richmond Times Dispatch, Tuesday November 26, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Crocodile- Russian Language Newspaper/Magazine 1973, 1979, 1982, 1983 (Box 33)
      1973: #3, 9, 11 - 12, 14 - 15, 17 - 19
      1979: #24 - 36
      1982: #25 - 27, 30 - 36
      1983: #1 - 4, 8, 25 - 36
    - Russian Language News Paper #310, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Russian Comic/Joke Book 2 issues, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Russian Language Newspaper #90, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Russian Language Magazine #45, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Russian Language Magazine #11, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Russian Language Magazine October 1976 (Box 33)
    - Crocodile- Russian Language Newspaper/Magazine 1984 (Box 34)
      1984: #1 -13, 15 - 25, 27 - 28, 30 - 36
    - Crocodile- Russian Language Newspaper/Magazine 1985 (Box 35)
      1985: #1 - 36
    - Crocodile- Russian Language Newspaper/Magazine 1986, 1987 (Box 36)
      1986: #1 - 36
      1987: #1 - 24, 34 - 36
    - Crocodile- Russian Language Newspaper/Magazine 1988 (Box 37)
      1988: #1 - 36
    - Crocodile- Russian Language Newspaper/Magazine 1989 (Box 38)
      1989: #1 - 33
    - El Adelanto, November 21, 1967 (Box 39)
    - El Adelanto, November 29, 1967 (Box 39)
    - El Adelanto, 1968 (MLK Assassinatin) (Box 39)
    - Insula, September 1967 (Box 39)
    - La Gaceta Regional, undated (Box 39)
    - La Gaceta Regional, November 29, 1967 (Box 39)
    - Michigan State News, September 1967 (Box 39)
    - Richmond News Leader, Daily Black and White Comics 1975, 1976 (Box 39)
      1975: September 25 - November 15
      1976: January 6 - 31
    - Sunday London Times, April 7, 1968 (MLK Assassination) (Box 39)
    - Sunday London Times Magazine, April 7, 1968 (Box 39)
    - Commonwealth Times, Vol. 6 #18, February 28, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Commonwealth Times, April 11-17, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Commonwealth Times, April 25-May1, 1978 (Box 40)
    - France Soir, January 9, 1976 (Box 40)
    - La Nacion, September 12, 1971 (Box 40)
    - Plain Truth, November 1, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Richmond News Leader, January 19, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Richmond News Leader, April 18, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Area/State/Perspective, August 10, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Parade, November 1, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Real Estate/Classified, June 18, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday Comics 1976, 1977 (Box 40)
      1976: May 16, 29
      1977: May 22
      June 5, 12, 19, 26
      July 3, 10, 17, 24, 31
      August 7, 28
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, July 2, 1977 (Box 40)
    - Press, The, Vol. 11 #3, August 1977 (Box 40)
    - Rolling Stone, #246, August 25, 1977 (Box 40)
    - Tennessean Sunday Showcase, August 3-9, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Treetop Tattler-Tribune, February 27, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Village Voice, December 22, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Washington Post Bookworld, September 19, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Harper's Weekly: Journal of Civilization, XXIII #1164, April 19, 1879 (Box Folder 41)
  - Sub-series D - Other Comic Related Items
    - Advertisements
      - Animatrix, undated (Box 42)
      - Another Rainbow Publishing, Inc., undated, 1984-1987, 1993-1996, 1999-2000 (Box 42)
      - Anotheruniverse.com, undated (Box 42)
      - Art of Jack Davis, The, 1987 (Box 42)
      - B. Kliban's "Cat Cards," 1978 (Box 42)
      - Barks Quicklist, The, 1982-1983 (Box 42)
      - Basil Wolverton Art for Sale, undated (Box 42)
      - Bud Plant, undated (Box 42)
      - Cel-Ebration!, undated (Box 42)
      - Chester Gould - Dick Tracy Museum Foundation, The, 2001 (Box 42)
      - Christie's East, 1993 (Box 42)
      - Cochran, Russ, undated, 1975, 1977, 1980 (Box 42)
      - Collection of Unrecorded Faulkner Translation, undated (Box 42)
      - Collector's Palace Catalogs, undated (Box 42)
      - Comics in the Classroom, 1977 (Box 42)
      - Comic Subscriptions, undated, 1972 (Box 42)
      - Corben Studios/Fantagor Press, undated (Box 42)
      - Crumb, R., undated (Box 42)
      - Custom Comic Service, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
      - DC Comics, 1983, 1984, 1988 (Box 42)
      - Double Diamond Press, undated (Box 42)
      - Drawn & Quarterly Publishers, 1999 (Box 42)
      - Drawn & Quarterly Promotional Postcards, undated, 1995 (Box 42)
      - EC Comics, undated (Box 42)
      - Eclipse Comics 1989-1990 (Box 42)
      - Encyclopedia of Comic Book Heroes, 1976 (Box 42)
      - Fandom.com, undated, 2000 (Box 42)
      - Fantagraphics Books Catalogs, undated (Box 42)
      - Fantasy Film Celebrity Convention, 1978 (Box 42)
      - FOOM - Friends of Ol' Marvel, undated, 1974 (Box 42)
      - G. Armani Society, 1994-1995 (Box 42)
      - Gemstone Publishing, 1999 (Box 42)
      - Gibb-Smith Publisher, 1997 (Box 42)
      - Gotham Graphics, 1995 (Box 42)
      - Graphixus, 1978 (Box 42)
      - Greater Buffalo the Press, 1977 (Box 42)
      - Hannes Bok Illustrations, undated (Box 42)
      - Heavy Metal Magazine, undated (Box 42)
      - Heroes Del Comics (Spain), 1991 (Box 42)
      - International Comics Festival, The, 1992 (Box 42)
      - Joe Kubert School of Cartoon & Graphic Art, 1980 (Box 42)
      - Lifetime Learning System, Inc., 1986 (Box 42)
      - Margo Feiden Galleries, Ltd., The, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, 1976, 1978, 1989, 1993, 1997 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Animation, undated, 1993 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Books, undated, 1977, 1978, 1983, 1998 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Books About Comics, undated, 1974, 1976, 1989, 1993, 2000 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Book Catalogs, undated, 1974 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Business Cards, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Catalogs, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Art For Sale, undated, 1978, 1981, 1983, 1986, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Book Shops, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Catalogs, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Convention Flyers, 1975, 1977 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comics for Sale, undated, 1989 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Order Forms, undated, 1978, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1991 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Posters, undated, 1983, 1987 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Subscriptions, undated, 1972 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Conference Order Forms, 1983 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Contests, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Disneyana, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Education, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Fanzine, undated, 1989 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Flyers, undated (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Magazine, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Membership Dues Forms, 1983 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Movie Reviews, 1990 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Museums, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Promotional Postcards, undated, 1975, 1991, 1994, 1997, 2000 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Price Guide Order Forms, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Science Fiction, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Video, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Video Games, undated (Box 43)
      - Museum of Cartoon Art Promotional Postcards, undated (Box 43)
      - National Clearing House for Alcohol Information, 1979 (Box 43)
      - National Lampoon, 1980 (Box 43)
      - Pacific Comics Club, undated, 1983, 1985, 1986 (Box 43)
      - Pogo Poster, undated (Box 43)
      - Political Graphics Service, undated (Box 43)
      - Raphael Soyer Illustrations, undated (Box 43)
      - Raw Magazine, undated (Box 43)
      - Rusty Riley Comic Panels for Sale, 1991 (Box 43)
      - Salvador Dali Art Prints, undated (Box 43)
      - Spiderman Reading Motivation Kit, The, undated (Box 43)
      - Spring Hollow Books, undated, 1998, 2001 (Box 43)
      - Stabur Graphics, Inc., undated (Box 43)
      - Star Trek, 1995 (Box 43)
      - Supersnipe: Comic Book & Art Catalog, 1977 (Box 43)
      - Tadcorps, 1991 (Box 43)
      - Tony Raiola (Box 43)
      - United States Postal Service, 1997 (Box 43)
      - Walt Disney, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
      - Walt Kelly Promotional Postcards, 1993, 1995 (Box 43)
      - WB Store Gallery News, 2000 (Box 43)
      - Wizard Magazine, undated, 1999, 2002 (Box 43)
      - Words & Pictures Museum Promotional Postcards, undated, 1993, 1994, 1996 (Box 43)
    - Artwork
      - Barks, Carl Reprint Guide, undated (Box 43)
      - Bookmark, undated (Box 43)
      - Brooks, Dick, undated (Box 43)
      - Cartoon Art Museum Collector's Prints, undated, 1985, 1989-1992, 1994, 1995, 1997 (Box 43)
      - Comic Books (photocopied), undated (Box 43)
      - Eisner, Will (photocopied), undated (Box 43)
      - Fett, George, 1975 (Box 43)
      - Funnies Paper, The, 2000 (Box 43)
      - Haagär, the Horrible, undated (Box 43)
      - International Museum of Cartoon Art Membership Print, undated (Box 43)
      - Kaluta, Michael, 1975 (Box 43)
      - Lee, Bill, undated (Box 43)
      - Marchesano, Vincent, 1971 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Comics (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Drawings, undated (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Comic Strips, undated (Box 43)
      - Newspaper Comic Strip, 1915 (Box 43)
      - Peters, Mike, 1997 (Box 43)
      - Richards, Ted, undated, 1980 (Box 43)
      - Scancarelli: Gasoline Alley: Wallet Family Tree, 1988 (Box 43)
      - Sojourn Artwork, undated, 1979 (Box 43)
      - Swan, Curt, 1975 (Box 43)
      - Wizard of Id Sample, 1989 (Box 43)
      - Wizard Magazine Comic Art Posters, undated (Box 43)
      - Wood, Wally, undated (Box 43)
    - Fan Clubs:
      - Bloom County Fan Club of America Newsletter, The, 1985 (Box 43)
      - Carl Barks Fan Club, undated 2000 (Box 43)
      - DC Comics Superman Club, 1980 (Box 43)
      - International Wizard of Oz, undated, 1974-1983, 1985, 1988 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 43)
      - National E. C. Fan Addict Club, undated 1954 (Box 43)
      - Pogo Fan Club, undated, 1980, 1988-1990, 1997, 2002 (Box 43)
      - Snoopy Fan Club, 1983 (Box 43)
      - Superman Fan Club, 1983 (Box 43)
      - Twin Peaks Gazette, 1991 (Box 43)
      - WAM (Wild Agents of Marvel), 1991 (Box 43)
    - Multimedia:
      - Heavy Metal FAKK2/KISS: Psycho Circus CD-ROM, undated (Box 43)
    - Organization:
      - Comic Magazine Association of America, Inc., undated, 1975-1976 (Box 43)
    - Other:
      - American Comic Book Exhibition, 1985 (Box 44)
      - Archive of Popular Culture (University of Pittsburgh), undated (Box 44)
      - Art of Cartoons Exhibition Program, The, 1987 (Box 44)
      - Artist and Writers Speakers Bureau, The, undated (Box 44)
      - Aurora Comic Scenes Instruction Booklet: The Amazing Spiderman, 1974 (Box 44)
      - Barks Foundation, The, 1983 (Box 44)
      - Berni Wrightson Catalog, The, 1977 (Box 44)
      - Bookplates, undated, 1972 (Box 44)
      - Buena Vista (Disney) Pictures Marketing Press Package, 1990 (Box 44)
      - Cartoon Art Museum, San Francisco, undated, 1987 (Box 44)
      - Cartoonist Exchange Certificate, 1951 (Box 44)
      - Chyrsler-Plymouth, Dodge Illustrator's Kit, 1975, 1976 (Box 44)
      - Chrysler-Plymouth, Dodge Illustrator's Kit, 1978 (Box 44)
      - Cinnamon Mini Buns Free DC Mini Comic, 1989 (Box 44)
      - Classcom, Inc., undated, 1989, 1990 (Box 44)
      - Collecting Animation Art, undated (Box 44)
      - Comic Art Convention, 1975 (Box 44)
      - Comic Book Guide for the Artist -- Writer -- Letterer, 1973 (Box 44)
      - Comic Book Shaped Erasers, undated (Box 44)
      - Comic Fanzine Adresses, undated (Box 44)
      - Comics in the Classroom, undated (Box 44)
      - Comics in the Classroom/DC Secret Origins, 1991 (Box 44)
      - Comic Samples with Explanatory Blurbs, undated (Box 44)
      - Complete Index to E. C. Comics, The, undated (Box 44)
      - Dodge Chrysler-Plymouth Illustrator's Kit, 1973 (Box 44)
      - Dodge Chrysler-Plymouth Illustrator's Kit, 1974 (Box 44)
      - DreamWeavers (Charles Vess), 1994 (Box 44)
      - E. C. Fan Addict Convention, 1975 (Box 44)
      - Edgar Rice Burroughs Quarterly, 1983 (Box 44)
      - Face Behind the Laugh: Self Portraits in Caricature, 1988 (Box 44)
      - Festival of Cartoon Art, The 1989 (Box 44)
      - Festival International de la Bande Dessinée, 1998 (Box 44)
      - Flashback Comic Strip Clippings, undated (Box 44)
      - Friends of Odkin/Wally Wood, 1980 (Box 44)
      - Funnies Paper, The, undated (Box 44)
      - Garfield Giftwrap, 1980 (Box 44)
      - Guide to the Popular Culture Collection at Bowling Green State University, 1978 (Box 44)
      - House of Humor and Satire, The, 1987 (Box 44)
      - Informal, In-Depth Conversation with Burne Hogarth, Gil Kane and Dick Hodgins, 1973 (Box 44)
      - International Comics and Animation Festival, 1995 (Box 44)
      - International Comics Festival, The, 1994 (Box 44)
      - International Museum of Cartoon Art Membership Packet, 1996, 1999, 2000 (Box 44)
      - Jews Comics, undated, 2001 (Box 44)
      - Joe Kubert School of Cartooning and Graphic Art, 1989 (Box 44)
      - John Wayne Comic Book Pages, 1950 (Box 44)
      - Kelly, Walt, undated, 1950 (Box 44)
      - Kingdom of Puppets, undated (Box 44)
      - King Features Catalog, 1974 (Box 44)
      - King Features Spanish/English Program Poster, undated (Box 44)
      - Kitchen Sink Press, 1995 (Box 44)
      - Lawrence Scripps Wilkinson Collection of Toys, 1986, 2002 (Box 44)
      - Library of Congress, 1995 (Box 44)
      - Little Nemo Christmas Cards, 1997 (Box 44)
      - Made in the U.S.A.: American Art Forms, 1977 (Box 44)
      - Mickey Mouse Stickers, undated (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Checklists, undated (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Checklists, undated (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Foreign Language Items, 1979 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Invoices, 1971, 1986, 1988, 1996 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Museums, undated (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Peanuts/Snoopy Items, undated (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Posters, undated, 1997, 1998 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Press Releases, 1997 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Stickers, undated, 1998 (Box 44)
      - Museum of Cartoon Art: Classic Comic Collection, undated (Box 44)
      - Museum of Cartoon Art Hall of Fame Poster, undated (Box 44)
      - National Gallery of Caricature and Cartoon Art, undated (Box 44)
      - Newspapers in the Classroom, undated (Box 44)
      - Official Index to the Doc Savage Pulp Adventures, 1975 (Box 44)
      - Pittsburgh Comix Club, undated (Box 44)
      - Placecards, undated (Box 44)
      - Pogo for President, 1980 (Box 44)
      - Popeye Patch, undated (Box 44)
      - Positive and Negative: Dominate Images of Aging in Daily Strips, undated (Box 44)
      - Price List Notebook, undated (Box 44)
      - R. Crumb Legal Fund, undated (Box 44)
      - R. Crumb Stickers, 1971 (Box 44)
      - Reference Cards for Books Donated, undated, 1992, 1993 (Box 44)
      - Roy Lichtenstein Greeting Cards, undated, 1972 (Box 44)
      - Russel B. Nye Popular Culture Collection at Michigan State University, 1978 - 1981 (Box 44)
      - 1990 (Box 44)
      - Segar, Elzie (Popeye), 1994 (Box 44)
      - Shadow Secret Society Bulletin, 1977 (Box 44)
      - Shoney Bear & His Friends, undated (Box 44)
      - Simpsons, The, 2000 (Box 44)
      - Society for Animation Studies Conference (Box 44)
      - SPX 2002 Official Program Guide, 2002 (Box 44)
      - Supplement to Illustrator's Kit, 1974 (Box 44)
      - Topps Chewing Gum Stickers, 1975 (Box 44)
      - Underground Comix List, undated (Box 44)
      - Various Artists Works in the Underground, undated (Box 44)
      - Victoria International Cartoon Festival, 1986 (Box 44)
      - Walt Disney World, undated, 1976 (Box 44)
      - Wexner Center for the Arts, 1992 (Box 44)
      - Wizard Magazine Items, undated (Box 44)
      - Words & Picture Museum, 1995, 1997 (Box 44)
      - X-Men: Xavier Institute for Higher Learning Diploma, undated (Box 44)
    - Other:
      - Duke Magazine, 2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Cartoons, Clippings, undated, 1992-1993 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous CBG Clipping Service, 1997 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous CBG Clipping Service, 1998 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Art Clippings, undated, 1984-1988 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Book Articles, 1994 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Book Clippings, undated, 1991-1993 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Clippings, undated 1985-1988 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Clippings, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Clippings, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Clippings, undated, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Clippings, 1999 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Comic Strip Clippings, undated, 1992-1993 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous News Clippings, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, undated, 1986-1989, 1992 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated, 2000-2002 (Box 45)